Guide to the Duke University Libraries Collection of Haggadot, 1200-2003 (bulk1900-2003)
Duke University Libraries Collection of Haggadot 1200-2003 (bulk 1900-2003
- Date List Series, 1200-2003
  - 1940-1949 Subseries, (76 items)
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1946., 22 cm. Illustrated.
      Published by Kibbutz Hashomer Hatzair, the Kibbutz federation of a Zionist youth movement. Non-traditional text with some traditional elements. Duke has two copies of this haggadah. Copy two contains hand written and stamped ceremonial directions in Hebrew.
    - Passover Haggadah / edited by Lazarus Goldschmidt; illustrations by Bruno Frost; translation by Paul Goodman, 1946., 29 cm. Illustrated.
      English and Hebrew. Includes song for unaccompanied voice: Had gadya.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1946., 24 cm. Illustrated.
      Hebrew date on the cover corresponds to 1946. Black and white drawings with first two pages colored in by hand. Non-traditional text which reflects the secular leanings of the early kibbutz community.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1946., 22 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Kibbutz Kefar Gil`adi Tel Hai, Israel
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1946-1947., 23 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1946-1947., 25 cm. Text only.
      Includes commentaries by Abraham ben Ze'ev Nahum Bornstein and Samuel Bornstein.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1946-1947., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Hebrew only. Handwritten non-traditional text. Duke has two copies of this Haggadah.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1946-1947., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Handwritten and mimeographed. Non-traditional text. Duke has two copies of this Haggadah.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah `al pi minhag Ashkenaz u-Sefarad / mugah u-mevo'ar `al yede Dani'el Goldschmidt, 1947., 22 cm. Text only.
      Annotated by Daniel Goldschidt.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah / Hadpasah meyuhedet me-et Mosad Keren Spero .., 1947., 24 cm. Illustrated.
      Published by the Spero Foundation to support their goal of advancing traditional Judaism through the publication and distribution of Jewish classics, educational literature and allied purposeful philanthopic [sic] activities. Issued for the Jews of Europe by Agudath Israel Youth Council of America.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1947., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Printed and distributed in Germany by the American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee.
    - Hagadah de Pesaj, illustrada: servicio para las noches del Seder sugun el rito tradicional: traducido al Español moderno con versos poeticos y explanaciones necesarias / traducido por Tibor H. Stern, 1947., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Kansas City, Missouri
      Spanish and Hebrew.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1947-1948., 24 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Kibbutz, Israel
      Non-traditional text. Illustrations relate to working and defending the land of Israel.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1947-1948., 25 cm. Text only.
      Commentary by Rabbi Abraham Isaac Kook.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1947-1948., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Kibbutz Kevutsat ha-Tsofim, Israel
      Handwritten and mimeographed. Non-traditional text with added ceremonial directions in green ink. Signed on cover by Yehudah Engel.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1947-1948., 20 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Kibbutz Kefar Giladi, Israel
      Written and Illustrated by Gidon Katsch. Handwritten and mimeographed. Non-traditional text.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1947-1948., 22 cm. Text only.
      Hebrew only. Printed for the American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee.
    - A naye Hagode shel Pesah, 1948., 22 cm. Illustrated.
      Yiddish and Hebrew. Includes music for voice and piano.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1948., 22 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Kibbutz Ramat Yohanan, Israel
    - Le-hag ha-herut 708, 1948., 24 cm. Illustrated.
      Illustrations by Arieh Alweil. Issued for soldies of the Haganah. Non-traditional text. Illustrations on page 15 show military figures from throughout Jewish history.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = Service for the first nights of Passover / with a revised English translation by Joseph Loewy and Joseph Guens, 1948., 25 cm. Illustrated.
      Published before the independence of Israel. Includes music for songs at the end.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: `im mavo gadol ve-he`arot shonot u-perush hadash / me'et Shevah Knebel, 1948., 23 cm. Text only.
      Hebrew with notes in Rashi script. Published by Philipp Feldheim. Listing of other Jewish texts published by Philipp Feldheim at the back.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah / `im targum u-mavo ve-he`arot be-lashon Italkit me-et Shavtai To'af = Haggadah di Pasqua / testo Ebraico con traduzione Italiana, introduzione e note di Alfredo S. Toaff; illustrata da Eva Romanin Jacur, 1948., 25 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Florence, Italy
      Italian and Hebrew. Includes music for a few songs, including the Hatikvah (Israeli national anthem).
    - [Hagadah li-yeladim] = The children's Haggadah / edited by Dr. A.M. Silbermann; illustrated by Ersin Singer; with a new translation in prose and verse by Mr. Isidore Wartski ... and Rev. Arthur Saul Super M.A.; and with a selection of Seder melodies, 1948., 30 cm. Illustrated.
      Several illustrations have movable parts. Includes songs for voices.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1948-1949., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Published by Kibbutz Hashomer Hatzair, the Kibbutz federation of a Zionist youth movement. Non-traditional text.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1948-1949., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Kibbutz Heftsi-bah, Israel
      Handwritten with a non-traditional text. Page 30 in a different hand than rest of Haggadah.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1948-1952., 22 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Kibbutz Nezer, Israel
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1949., 25 cm. Illustrated.
      English and Hebrew. Fundraising tool for Yeshivas Ohel Torah. Includes photographs of students studying, playing basketball, and playing ping pong on center pages.
    - Bibliographie der Oster-Haggadah, 1500-1900 / von S. Wiener, 1949., 29 cm. Text only.
      Bibliography of Haggadot from 1500-1900. Hebrew with some German. Includes three loose pieces of paper with English handwritten notes about specific Haggadot and the history of the Haggadah.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah / [edited by] Pablo Link, 1949., 21 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Buenos Aires
      Hebrew and Spanish with ceremonial directions; notes and introduction in Spanish.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = Passover Hagadah / translated by Z. Harry Gutstein, 1949., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Passover Hagadah = Hagadah shel Pesah / translated by Z. Harry Gutstein, 1949., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Haggadah of Passover / a faithful English rendering by Abraham Regelson; illustrated by Siegmund Forst, 1949., 16 cm. Illustrated.
      Gift of the Yeshiva & Mesifta Toras Chaim of Greater New York. Printed in honor of the first Passover in the modern State of Israel as a fundraising tool. The request for donations is found in both English (back inside cover) and Yiddish (front inside cover). The illustrations near the end of the Haggadah (pp. 53, 57) connect the text of the seder to the pioneering efforts in the new state of Israel.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Haggadah of Passover / a faithful English rendering by Abraham Regelson; illustrated by Siegmund Forst, 1949., 15 cm. Illustrated.
      Exclusively produced as a Gift to the Friends and Supporters of the General Israel Orphans' Home for Girls, Jerusalem, Israel ...--Cover. Printed in honor of the first Passover by the modern State of Israel as a fundraising tool. The request for donations is found in both English (back inside cover) and Yiddish (front inside cover). The illustrations near the end of the Haggadah (pp. 53, 57) connect the text of the seder to the pioneering efforts in the new state of Israel.
    - [Hagadah shel Pesah] = The Pessach Haggadah / illuminated by Kafra, 1949., 31 cm. Illuminated.
      Illuminated in the Medieval style. Duke has two copies of this Haggadah.
    - [Hagadah shel Pesah] = The Haggadah of Passover / a faithful English rendering by Abraham Regelson; illustrated by Siegmund Forst, 1949., 32 cm. Illustrated.
      Supplemental text in Hebrew and English. Includes Israel's Proclamation of Independence in both Hebrew and English. With the traditional songs of the Haggadah composed and arranged by Cantor Joshua S. Weisser.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1949-1950., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1949-1950., 22 cm. Illustrated.
      Handwritten and illustrated by Arieh Alweil. Published by the Israeli Military Rabbinic Association for Israeli soldiers.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1949-1950., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Kibbutz 'En Harod, Israel
      Illustrations are reproductions of Haim Atar's murals in the kibbutz's dining room. Non-traditional text.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1949-1950., 20 cm. Illustrated.
      Includes illustrations from older Haggadot.
    - Le-hag ha herut: perakim, 1949-1950., 24 cm. Illustrated.
      Hebrew only. Several essays about Passover. Includes special Passover laws for soldiers. Published by the Israeli army.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Passover Haggadah / with a new translation by Saadyah Maximon; and illustrations by Paul K. Freeman, 1949-1950., 16 cm. Illustrated.
      Used as a fundraising tool for the General Israel Orphans' Home for Girls.
    - Hagadah for Passover = Hagadah shel Pesah, 1949-1950., 17 cm. Illustrated.
      Used as an advertising tool by Streit's Matzos.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 194-?., 25 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Kibbutz Kefar Monash, Israel
      Handwritten and illustrated by Gidon Katsch.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 194-?., 27 cm. Illustrated.
      Non-Traditional text with traditional elements. Handwritten and mimeographed.
    - Aviv, 194-?., 21 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Kibutz, Israel
      Hebrew only. Handwritten, non-traditional text.
    - Passover Hagadah = Hagadah Shel Pesah: with English translation, 194-?., 23 cm. Text only.
      Hebrew and English. Includes some small sketches. Duke has two copies of this Haggadah.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 194-?., 22 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Kibbutz Afikim, Israel
      Handwritten non-traditional text.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 194-?., 24 cm. Illustrated.
      Handwritten non-traditional text. Page 10 (Hebrew numbers) with stylized illustration of Hebrew slaves and of free Hebrews leaving Egypt carrying unleavened dough on their heads. Page 10 (Arabic numbers) shows full page illustration of ship off coast of mandate Palestine at night with illegal immigrants coming ashore.
  - 1950-1959 Subseries, (62 items)
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = Service for the first nights of Passover / with a revised English translation by Joseph Loewy and Joseph Guens, 1950., 25 cm. Illustrated.
      Bound in black cloth with padded boards, raised leaf design, cover and spine titles stamped in gold, tooled copper view of David's Tower from the wall of Jerusalem's old city outlined in gold stamping on upper board, and binder's name stamped in gold beneath copper tooling: Betsalel, Yerushalayim.
    - The Passover Haggadah. supplemented by one hundred chapters ... arranged and edited by Menachem M. Kasher, 1950., 24 cm. Illustrated.
    - Sefer Hagadah shel Pesah: ... minhag Djerba ... u-piyut Had gadya ... be-lashon `Aravi, 1950., 22 cm. Text only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1950-1951., 20 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1950-1951., 24 cm. Illustrated.
      Hebrew and Yiddish. Includes photographs and sketches of well-known rabbis as an illustration for the Rabbis from B'nei Barak.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1950-1951., 25 cm. Illustrated.
    - Seder shel Pesah nosah Yagur, 1951., 25 cm. Text only.
      Music only. Music by Yehudah Sharett. For celebrants, solo voices (SATB), mixed choir, children's choir, and instrumental ensemble.
    - [Hagadah shel Pesah] = The haggadah of Passover / a faithful English rendering by Abraham Regelson; illustrated by Siegmund Forst, 1951., 16 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Passover Haggadah / with a new English translation by Isidore Fishman .., 1951., 21 cm. Text only.
      English and Hebrew with ceremonial directions and notes in English. Illustrations signed by Herz.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: Ma`ase le-melekh ... / mi-ketav yad she-katav ve-tsayar Mosheh b.R. Natan ha-Kohen ...; ha-perush Ma`ase le-melekh ... / `a.y. Tsevi Ya`akov 'Avraham, 1951., 24 cm. Illustrated.
      Includes facsimile of: Seder Hagadah shel Pesah ... / 'Ani Mosheh b.mo.h. Natan ha-Kohen katavti zo't ve-gamarti from 1816.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Haggadah of Passover / a faithful English rendering by Abraham Regelson; illustrated by Siegmund Forst, 1951., 14 cm. Illustrated.
      Printed as a fundraising tool. The request for donations is found in both English (back inside cover) and Yiddish (front inside cover). Exclusively produced as a Gift to the Friends and Supporters of the General Israel Orphans' Home for Girls, Jerusalem, Israel, ...--Cover. Duke has three copies of this Haggadah.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = Hagadah: Passover Seder Service, 1951., 14 cm. Illustrated.
      Compliments of Maxwell House Coffee and Instant Maxwell House Coffee. Prepared by Joseph Jacobs Jewish Market Organization, New York, N.Y.--Cover. Duke has two of these Haggadot.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1951-1952., 37 cm. Illustrated.
      Hebrew text. English translation included as an insert. Written and decorated by J. Zimberknopf.
    - The Pessah Hagada, 1951-1952., 41 cm. Illustrated.
      This Hagada, printed in Jerusalem by Hamadpis Liphshitz Press, is a reproduction of an old Venetian edition ... It contained an Italian translation, for which English has been substituted.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Pessah Hagada, 1951-1952., 42 cm. Illustrated.
      English and Hebrew. Facsimile of Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: bi-leshon ha-kodesh u-fitrono bi-leshon Ashkenazim ... Venitsiyah: Stamperia Vendramina, 501 [1740 or 1741]. This Hagada--printed in Jerusalem by Hamadpis Lipshitz Press, is a reproduction of an old Venetian edition of which the above [as in Facsimile note] is the original title page. It contained an Italian [?] translation, for which English has been substituted--Colophon. Ha-tseva`im veha-tsiurim ve-seder ha-`amudim hut`amu le-tavnit ha-hotsa'at"--Colophon. "`Al ha-kerikhah tsiur Ha lahma `anya bi-tseva`im mi-tokh Hagadat Sarayevo--Yaari. Yaari 2416.
    - Passover Korea, 1952, 1952?., 21 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: United States
      For the use of American Jewish soldiers serving in Korea.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Passover Haggadah: for Jewish personnel in the U.S. Armed Forces and Veterans Administration hospitals, 1952., 18 cm. Illustrated.
      English and Hebrew. Uses the illuminated letters from the 1923 edition of the Union Haggadah. Duke has two copies of this Haggadah.
    - The Haggadah for children / prepared by Jacob P. Rudin, 1952., 19 cm. Illustrated.
      Illustrated by R. Leaf. Includes music arranged by Prof. A.W. Binder.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1952-1953., 18 cm. Illustrated.
      This Haggadah was written and illustrated by David Alef.
    - The Passover Haggadah / with English translation, introduction, and commentary based on the commentaries of E.D. Goldschmidt; edited by Nahum N. Glatzer, 1953., 24 cm. Illustrated.
      Translation of the Haggadah text by Jacob Sloan, illustrated with woodcuts from the first illuminated Haggadah, Prague, 1526--T.p. verso.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah tsum driten seder fun Histadrut kampayn / geshriben fun Avrohom Tverski; stsenirt un rezsimirt fun Tsevi Skoler; muzik unter der leytung fun N.L. Zoslovski, 1953., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Yiddish and Hebrew. The Hagadah for the Third Seder was written under the impact of the great event in Jewish history which took place six years ago--the creation of the State of Israel (p. 4). Mostly an original text with some traditional elements.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = Passover Haggadah / a faithful English rendering by Abraham Regelson; illustrated by Siegmund Forst, 1953., 21 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = Passover Haggadah / a faithful English rendering by Abraham Regelson; illustrated by Siegmund Forst, 1953., 21 cm. Illustrated.
      Cover contains advertisements of the Home of the Sages of Israel. Imperfect copy: P. 3-12, 17-18, 21-24, 27-28 lacking; bottom half of p. 15-16, 33-34, 41-42, 57-64 cut away. Cover contains advertisements of the Home of the Sages of Israel
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1953-1954., 34 cm. Illustrated.
      Illustrated by Jacob Wechsler. Note on the front page indicates that the Haggadah was a gift to Dr. Pascher from Harold Scheinberg.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1953-1954., 24 cm. Illustrated.
      Text in English, Hebrew, and Yiddish; introduction in English.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah: `im hamishah `asar perushim .., 1953-1954., 23 cm. Text only.
      Commentaries by Rashi, et al.
    - Seder Hagadah shel Pesah, 1954., 17 cm. Text only.
      Includes commentaries by Moses Sofer, Samuel Ehrenfeld and David Tsevi Ehrenfeld. Reprint of the original which was published in Viena in 1883-1884.
    - Pessach-Haggadah / bearbeitet von Robert Raphael Geis, 1954., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: [Düsseldorf-Benrath?], Germany
      Text in German and Hebrew; ceremonial directions in German. Includes illustrations from older Haggadot.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: service for the first nights of Passover / 17 illustrations in colour by A. Allweil, an essay by Max Brod and an accompanying text by I.M. Lask; with a revised English translation and copious explanatory notes by Joseph Loewy and Joseph Guens, 1954., 27 cm. Illustrated.
      Plates printed on separate paper and mounted on leaves.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The Haggadah of Passover, 1954., 16 cm. Illustrated.
      Hebrew and English.
    - The model seder / prepared by Harry Nelson and Harry Malin, 1954., 21 cm. Illustrated.
      English and Hebrew. Changes made to make the seder more meaningful for the children (p. 3). Includes photographs of Jewish art and ritual objects.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1954-1955., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Kibbutz Giv€˜at Brener, Israel
      Non traditional text.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1955., 28 cm. Illustrated.
      English and Hebrew. Includes a special section for children.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: `im mador meyuhad li-yeladim "Ve-higadeta le-vinkha" / `arukh `al yede Sh.S.; tiken, `iter ve-tsiyer Ts. Livni, 1955., 28 cm. Illustrated.
      Bound in white leather with padded upper board, tooled copper plate with title, Hagadah shel Pesaòh, outlined in gold stamping on upper board, in the style of Betzalel.
    - Passover Haggadah / Washington Hebrew Congregation, 1955., 28 cm. Text only.
      Location: Washington D.C.
      Typed on a typewriter and stapled together. Adapted from Union prayer book--Leaf [1].
    - The Haggadah for children / prepared by Jacob P. Rudin, 1955., 19 cm. Illustrated.
      Illustrations by R. Leaf. English and/or Hebrew.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1955-1956., 24 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Kibbutz Merhavyah, Israel
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = The haggadah of Passover, 1956., 16 cm. Illustrated.
      Illustrated by Siegmund Forst. Fundraising tool for the United Charity Institutions of Jerusalem.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah: service for the first nights of Passover / with a revised English translation and copious explanatory notes by Joseph Loewy and Joseph Guens; with coloured illustrations, 1956., 32 cm. Illustrated.
      Illustrations by Alvail. Plates printed on separate paper and mounted on leaves.
    - Hagadah for Passover = Hagadah shel Pesah, 1956-1957., 17 cm. Illustrated.
      English and Hebrew. Published by Borden's as an advertising tool.
    - Haggadah for young people / by Martha Marenof, 1957., 22 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Boston, Massachussetts
      Reads from left to right.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1958., 17 x 25 cm. Illustrated.
      Illustrated by Moshe Proops and handwritten by Mordekhai Amitai. Includes musical instructions.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1958., 92 mm. x 13 cm. Illustrated.
      Slip mounted on p. 4 of cover indicates Haggadah distributed to participants in Passover tour 1929 April 22 to 1959 May 3.
    - Samaritan Haggada and Pessah Passover: Zevah korban ha-Pesah, 1958., 24 cm. Text only.
      Haggadah contains the Samaritan ceremony for the Passover sacrifice. Text is written in the Paleo-Hebrew script still used by the Samaritan community, as well as the square Hebrew script.
    - Haggadah for the American family: ... including a new complete English service with directions ... and Hebrew text / English service written by Martin Berkowitz, 1958., 22 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Merion, Pennsylvania
      Martin Berkowitz was the Rabbi of Temple Adath Israel of the Main Line in Merion, Pennsylvania. Duke has two copies of this Haggadah.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1958-1959., 27 cm. Illustrated.
      English and Hebrew. Music arranged by Solomon Rosowsky.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1958-1959., 17 cm. Illustrated.
    - [Hagadah shel Pesah] = Passover Haggadah: with explanatory notes and original readings: new translation / compiled and edited by Rabbi Morris Silverman; designed and illustrated by Ezekiel Schloss, 1959., 24 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Hartford, Connecticut
    - Hagadah shel Pesah = Passover Haggadah / a faithful English rendering by A. Regelson; illustrations by S. Forst, 1959., 16 cm. Illustrated.
      Printed as a fundraising tool. The request for donations is found in both English (back inside cover) and Yiddish (front inside cover). The obviously Zionistic illustrations from earlier editions of the Haggadah (see Haggadah Pam 12 mo #15) are missing from this edition.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1959., 17 cm. Text only.
      Hebrew Only. A sticker with Hebrew writing on the back reveals that it was intended for the participants of a tour group celebrating passover from 1959 April 22-1959 May 3.
    - Hagadah shel pesah = Passover Haggadah: with explanatory notes and original readings: new translation / compiled and edited by Morris Silverman; designed and illustrated by Ezekiel Schloss, 1959., 24 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 1959-60., 17 cm. Illustrated.
      Location: Kefar Gil'adi, Israel
      Hebrew only.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 195-?., 23 cm. Illustrated.
      Non traditional text with traditional elements.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 195-?., 22 cm. Text only.
      Location: Kibbutz Alummot, Israel
      Non-traditional text. Hebrew without vowels.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 195-?., 23 cm. Illustrated.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 195-?., 18 x 25 cm. Illustrated.
      Illustrated by Ze'ev. This Haggadah was an insert in the Maariv [Israeli] newspaper.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 195-?., 19 cm. Illustrated.
      Handwritten and illustrated by David Alef and Ayelet ha-Shahar. Non-traditional text.
    - Hagadah shel ha-Seneh le-Pesah, 195-?., 16 x 17 cm. Illustrated.
      Illustrated by Iris Shviitser. Non-traditional text written to emphasize the security provided by the Seneh, an Israeli security organization.
    - Seder lel hitkadesh hag: Hagadah shel Pesah... / ...perush...Avraham Shemu'el Binyamin Sofer...; midreshe Hazal...ve-likute halakhot...Ya`akov Lisa, 195-?., 22 cm. Illustrated.
      Hebrew only. Includes a number of pictures of well-known rabbis on the pages preceding and following the Haggadah text.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 195-?., 20 cm. Illustrated.
      This Haggadah was handwritten and illustrated by David Alef. Non-traditional text. Duke owns two copies of this Haggadah.
    - Hagadah shel Pesah, 195-?., 24 cm. Illustrated.